The Western Lore
Desperate Riders is a western, action, drama film directed by Michael Feifer.
After Kansas Red rescues young Billy from a card-game shootout, the boy asks Red for help
protecting his family from the outlaw Thorn, who’s just kidnapped Billy’s mother, Carol.
As Red and Billy ride off to rescue Carol, they run into beautiful,
tough-as-nails Leslie, who’s managed to escape Thorn’s men.
The three race to stop Thorn’s wedding to Carol with guns
a-blazing - but does she want to be rescued?
Kansas Red, played by Drew Waters.
Thorn, played by Trace Adkins.
Doc Tillman, played by Tom Berenger.
Leslie, played by Vanessa Evigan.
Billy, played by Sam Ashby.
Carol, played by Victoria Pratt.
Desperate Riders is an American Western film, which was released in 2022.
The tone is emotional.